blz.in 2010-11-20

# Blaze Web Services Private Limited - Privacy Policy

                                    Blaze Web Services Private Limited - Privacy Policy
General:
Blaze Web Services Private Limited is committed to protecting your privacy. This document
will explain to you our policies for collecting, using, and disclosing personally identifiable
information that you provide to us. By submitting your personally identifiable information
to us you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Why We Collect/How We May Use Personally identifiable Information:
We collect personally identifiable information in order to, among other things,
(a) set up and provide services to our customers,
(b) process customer payments,
(c) improve our services, and
(d) communicate with our customers
.
Sources of Personally identifiable Information:
We receive and collect personally identifiable information from a variety of sources as we
interact with our customers and with the public. These sources include:
      E-mails, correspondence, and applications we receive from all sources.
      Cookies, URLs, web beacons, and other web identifiers we receive from visitors to
        our web sites.
      Credit card and credit information we receive as part of our billing and collection
        functions.
      Telephone calls, chat sessions, and blog postings we receive from all sources.
      Account information provided by our customers.
Note that we may receive personally identifiable information at sites both in the United
States and in other countries (where privacy laws may be less stringent).
What Information We May Collect: Due to the nature of our business, we collect a wide
variety of personally identifiable information, including:
      Personal data such as individual names, addresses, telephone numbers, credit card
        numbers, and e-mail addresses.
      Business data such as business names, addresses, telephone numbers, credit card
        numbers, and e-mail addresses.
      Non-personally identifiable information for aggregation such as, among other
        things, visitor browser type and screen resolution.
Information We May Disclose To Third Parties: Blaze Web Services Private Limited does
not sell or rent any personally identifiable information we collect to third parties. However,
we may disclose or transmit personally identifiable information to third parties for specific
purposes and situations, including:

In response to a subpoena, court order, or other valid legal process. To process or collect
customer payments.
     To enable third-party vendors to provide specific services to Blaze Web Services
        Private Limited, including, among others, retargeted ad placement services and
        website tracking, recording, testing, and optimization services.
     To prevent, investigate, or stop illegal or malicious activities including violations of
        our acceptable use policy, threats to our facilities, and threats to the physical safety of
        any person.
     To our affiliated companies or to any entity that acquires majority control of us
        or one of our business units through merger, acquisition, consolidation, or
        otherwise.
E-Mail Opt-Out: You may opt-out of receiving most e-mails from us by following the
“unsubscribe” instructions provided in the e-mails.
Minors: The Blaze Web Services Private Limited website is not designed to be used by
minors under 18 years old. It is not our intent to gather personally identifiable information
about anyone below the age of 18.
Appropriate Procedures: We have put in place reasonable measures and appropriate
procedures for implementing these policies and for safeguarding the information we collect
from you. However, we cannot guarantee that personally identifiable information we
collect will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.
Questions:If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us
at privacy@blz.in
